<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>YU-Chieh Kuo on Yu-Chieh Jesse Kuo</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in YU-Chieh Kuo on Yu-Chieh Jesse Kuo</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://ujkuo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Economic Analysis of Social Networks</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/sn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/sn/</guid><description>Economic Analysis of Social Networks This is a Ph.D.-level field course taught by Prof. Chih-Sheng Hsieh.
Here is my term project.</description></item><item><title>Information Economics</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/info_econ/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/info_econ/</guid><description>Information Economics This course was taught by Prof. Ling-Chieh Kung.
Here is my term project.</description></item><item><title>My Terminal Setting on M2 Macbook Air</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/temp/terminalsetting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/temp/terminalsetting/</guid><description>Thanks for the applications stuffs, research works, TOEFL and the incoming new semester, I cannot enjoy my new m2 Macbook Air received at early August. I used to use TimeMachine to transfer all applications and
the professor thg</description></item><item><title>Write-up for Corporate Finance Policies and Social Network</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/posts/corpfinnetwork/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/posts/corpfinnetwork/</guid><description>Write-up for Corporate Finance Policies and Social Network tags: Research paper link Main discovery Managers are influenced by their social peers when making decisions since they share the information in the low cost. The more social connection two companies share, the more similar both their level and change over time in investment. More connected firms show better economic performance. Robust even after controlling for industry variable. Explanation: Not only the company is influenced by their social connections but also they observe their competitive position in the network to make better policy.</description></item><item><title>Write-up for Ownership Network and Firm Growth</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/posts/ownershipnetwork/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/posts/ownershipnetwork/</guid><description>Write-up for Ownership Network and Firm Growth tags: Research Main Discovery Entering the ownership network and increase in network centrality, both globally and locally, are associated with higher future firm growth. Such effect of network position is more significant for high productivity firms and non-state-owned enterprises (non-SOE, 非國有企業), which have financial constraints. Eigenvector centrality has the largest economic impact and degree centrality is closely large. 1 std improvement in eigenvector centrality increases 16.</description></item></channel></rss>