<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>course on Yu-Chieh Jesse Kuo</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/tags/course/</link><description>Recent content in course on Yu-Chieh Jesse Kuo</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="http://ujkuo.github.io/tags/course/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Algorithms</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/algo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/algo/</guid><description>Algorithms I took both undergrad- and Ph.D.-level algorithms courses at NTU. The attachments below are part of my solutions to correspond assignments for the undergrad-level class. Both classes’ remaining coursework and lecture notes will be organized and uploaded sooner.
These two courses mainly teach algorithms from a theoretical perspective. In these algorithm courses, I learned the most about thinking and the skills of algorithm analysis, the logic and correctness verification of algorithm, the optimization analysis of algorithm, and how to design algorithm.</description></item><item><title>East Asian Confucianisms: Humanism</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/confucian/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/confucian/</guid><description>East Asian Confucianisms: Humanism This course explores the core values and development of East Asian Confucian cultural traditions from a modern perspective and analyzes its modern implications. Additionally, this course examines the humanistic spirit of East Asian Confucianism, including the life wisdom of Confucius, Mencius, Zhuzi, Japanese and Korean Confucians, and the life wisdom of Taoism and Buddhism as a Confucian contrasting and interactive system.
Here is my term project (written in Chinese).</description></item><item><title>Econometrics Theory</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/metrics_theory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/metrics_theory/</guid><description>Econometrics Theory I took the Ph.D.-level econometrics theory courses at NTU. The attachments below are my course notes.
This part of econometrics theory goes through topics in the classic Hansen and Hayashi textbooks, including GLS, Non-linear LS, constrained LS, Bayesian, etc.
Note 1 / Note 2 / Note 3 / Note 4 / Note 5 / Note 7</description></item><item><title>Game-theoretic Approach Marketing</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/mkt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/mkt/</guid><description>Game-theoretic Approach Marketing This is a doctoral course at the Graduate School of Business. It mainly leads students to approach marketing from the perspective of structural models, and uses game theory as the main analytical tool. In this class, we surveyed several marketing papers, in which I reported the findings of The Beneficial Effects of Ad Blockers and Media Platforms’ Content Provision Strategies and Sources of Profits, and discussed with the instructor the strengths and weaknesses of the model design and the results in the papers.</description></item><item><title>Information Economics</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/info_econ/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/info_econ/</guid><description>Information Economics This course was taught by Prof. Ling-Chieh Kung.
Here is my term project.</description></item></channel></rss>