<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Course experience on Yu-Chieh Jesse Kuo</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/</link><description>Recent content in Course experience on Yu-Chieh Jesse Kuo</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="http://ujkuo.github.io/course/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Algorithms</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/algo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/algo/</guid><description>Algorithms I took both undergrad- and Ph.D.-level algorithms courses at NTU. The attachments below are part of my solutions to correspond assignments for the undergrad-level class. Both classes’ remaining coursework and lecture notes will be organized and uploaded sooner.
These two courses mainly teach algorithms from a theoretical perspective. The topic of these courses include the time complexity analysis, dynamic programming, graph theory, (some of) approximation algorithms, and P versus NP problems.</description></item><item><title>East Asian Confucianisms: Humanism</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/confucian/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/confucian/</guid><description>East Asian Confucianisms: Humanism This course explores the core values and development of East Asian Confucian cultural traditions from a modern perspective and analyzes its modern implications. Additionally, this course examines the humanistic spirit of East Asian Confucianism, including the life wisdom of Confucius, Mencius, Zhuzi, Japanese and Korean Confucians, and the life wisdom of Taoism and Buddhism as a Confucian contrasting and interactive system.
Here is my term project (written in Chinese).</description></item><item><title>Econometrics</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/metrics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/metrics/</guid><description>Econometrics I took the Ph.D.-level econometrics theory course at NTU. The econometrics theory includes four parts, and the attachments below are my course notes for words on blackboard in one parts of courses. This part goes through topics in the classic Hansen and Hayashi textbooks, including Asymptotic Theory, Prediction Errors, Model Selections, Non-linear LS, GMM, Constrained LS, Hypothesis Testing, Minimum Distance Estimators, James-Stein Estimator, Bayesian, with a theoretical perspective. Other parts of this course include OLS, GLS, 2SLS, SEM, MLE, M-Estimation, and Casual Inference.</description></item><item><title>Economic Analysis of Social Networks</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/sn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/sn/</guid><description>Economic Analysis of Social Networks Course Description This is a Ph.D.-level field course taught by Prof. Chih-Sheng Hsieh. The course starts from the characterization of networks, then enters into diverse topics for networks: network interactions, static and dynamic network formation, network sampling, and community detection. We mainly discuss tens of empirical research to introduce the data type and famous datasets for network analysis and find significant evidence about how peer effects affect us.</description></item><item><title>Game-theoretic Approach Marketing</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/mkt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/mkt/</guid><description>Game-theoretic Approach Marketing This is a doctoral course at the Graduate School of Business. It mainly leads students to approach marketing from the perspective of structural models, and uses game theory as the main analytical tool. In this class, we surveyed several marketing papers, in which I reported the findings of The Beneficial Effects of Ad Blockers and Media Platforms’ Content Provision Strategies and Sources of Profits, and discussed with the instructor the strengths and weaknesses of the model design and the results in the papers.</description></item><item><title>Information Economics</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/info_econ/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/info_econ/</guid><description>Information Economics This course was taught by Prof. Ling-Chieh Kung. The course aims to explore the incentives and decision-making process of different decision-makers under the condition of information asymmetry. For example, we explore how manufacturers make decisions about different selling channels in the supply chain. In the multi-sided platform, how the platform decides the best pricing and business strategy among the incentive and utility maximization problems of all players involved - consumers, platforms, and delivery staff - is also a topic that we are very concerned about.</description></item><item><title>Online Machine Learning</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/prediction_learning_and_games/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/prediction_learning_and_games/</guid><description>Prediction, Learning, and Games Online Machine Learning This course was taught by Prof. Yen-Huan Li . The course studies the online learning problem and its extensions from several aspects. The topics include Blackwell approachability, PAC-Bayes analysis, probability forecasting with the logarithmic loss, online portfolio selection, and learning with expert advice (from course website).
The course&amp;rsquo;s three assignments and the final project all include extensive literature reviews. For hw0, we first did a preliminary literature review in this field to understand the topics that are currently being studied in online machine learning.</description></item><item><title>Taoism: Zhuang Zhou</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/taosian/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/taosian/</guid><description>Taoism: Zhuang Zhou This course leads students into the philosophical thought world of Zhuang Zhou and Taoism. Zhuang Zhou is a well-known Chinese philosopher, whose depth and breadth of thinking are highly respected by everyone. Taoism is the thought that I follow and admire the most, and it has greatly influenced my outlook on life. I was honored to be able to enter the world of Taoism and Zhuang Zhou under the teaching of one of my favorite college teachers - Professor Lu Guizhen.</description></item><item><title>Text Mining</title><link>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/text_mining/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ujkuo.github.io/course/text_mining/</guid><description>Text Mining This course was taught by Prof. Chien-Chin Chen.
The term project &amp;ndash; Political Sentiment Analysis: A Survey of U.S. Media’s Attitude toward China Before and After the Presidential Election (written in Chinese) &amp;ndash; aims to analyze whether media attitudes toward China differ before and after the election.
This article combs through the US media’s reports related to China on Twitter, and applies BERT package to conduct sentiment analysis on the media&amp;rsquo;s reports.</description></item></channel></rss>